<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Sharp Traveler</title>
    <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Sharp Traveler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thesharptraveler.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A bump in the road</title>
      <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/a-bump-in-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/a-bump-in-the-road/</guid>
      <description>Today is the day that I was to leave to begin my trip. Unfortunately, that did not happen.
About ten days ago, I took a clumsy slip off of a trailer that was wet after a rainstorm. A minor injury, I said to myself. To be on the safe side, I took a trip to urgent care. It turns out that the &amp;ldquo;minor&amp;rdquo; injury was a fracture to my fifth metatarsal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventure</title>
      <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/the-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/the-adventure/</guid>
      <description>I am preparing for a year-long adventure across Europe and Asia. During this travel, I aim to explore and experience new cultures, meet new people, and learn more about myself. The journey will begin on July 12th as I travel to my first destination: Barcelona, Spain 🇪🇸
From there I will spend a month, using Barcelona as a home base to explore other areas of Spain and the surrounding countries. Aside from that first destination, the rest of the trip is largely unplanned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesharptraveler.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi 👋 my name is William Sharp! I am a Software Engineer, Technology Leader, and Business Owner. I’ve decided that now is the best time to embrace change. I’m traveling to Europe and Asia for a year. During this adventure, I hope to learn new things, embrace new cultures, and meet new people.
Follow this blog to join me in my adventure. I have no idea what I&amp;rsquo;m doing, but we&amp;rsquo;ll figure it out along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
