<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Sharp Traveler</title>
    <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Sharp Traveler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Packing</title>
      <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/packing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/packing/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to take this trip with a minimal mindset by only traveling with a backpack and a day bag. For this process, I drew inspiration from the subreddit /r/onebag For my backpacks I&amp;rsquo;ve selected:
Osprey Farpoint 40 Osprey Daylite Plus What am I bringing? Clothes (5) Gilden Crewneck T-Shirts (5) Under Armour Men&amp;rsquo;s Tech 6-inch Boxerjock (3) Darn Tough No Show Running Socks (2) Darn Tough Crew Socks (1) Rainleaf Microfiber Towel (1) Multifunctional Merino Wool Neckware Organization Compression Packing Cubes Matador FlatPak Waterproof Toiletry Case Electronics Macbook Pro 16 inch Anker PowerCore Slim 10K MagSafe Charger (2) International Travel Plug Adapter Various cables for connectivity and charging Documentation Passport in a case with Airtag Photocopies of driver&amp;rsquo;s license and passport Misc Locker lock for Hostels Carabiners Airtags in backpacks for security What am I buying when I arrive Some things I&amp;rsquo;ve decided are best to buy when I arrive to improve the ease of travel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A bump in the road</title>
      <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/a-bump-in-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/a-bump-in-the-road/</guid>
      <description>Today is the day that I was to leave to begin my trip. Unfortunately, that did not happen.
About ten days ago, I took a clumsy slip off of a trailer that was wet after a rainstorm. A minor injury, I said to myself. To be on the safe side, I took a trip to urgent care. It turns out that the &amp;ldquo;minor&amp;rdquo; injury was a fracture to my fifth metatarsal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventure</title>
      <link>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/the-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thesharptraveler.com/blog/2023/the-adventure/</guid>
      <description>I am preparing for a year-long adventure across Europe and Asia. During this travel, I aim to explore and experience new cultures, meet new people, and learn more about myself. The journey will begin on July 12th as I travel to my first destination: Barcelona, Spain 🇪🇸
From there I will spend a month, using Barcelona as a home base to explore other areas of Spain and the surrounding countries. Aside from that first destination, the rest of the trip is largely unplanned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
